Look at this.
見て、これ
season.
季節
A sense of the season.
季節感が
It's already over though.
もう終わってるけど
nice.
いいね
Nice, guys.
いいね、君たち
You guys are so cute.
可愛いね、あんたたち
It's perfect.
完璧だ
Grishmansu is over.
グリッシュマンス終わったけど
It's over though.
終わったけど
Shall we take a picture?
撮 ろうか
nice.
いいね
Peace, peace.
ピース、ピース
I just want this though.
ちょっと俺これ欲しいんだけど
This mushroom.
このキノコ
Combine the two of us.
2人の力を合わせて
Do something.
何 とかして
Can you go?
いけるか?
This guy is huge.
でかいわ、こいつ
heavy.
重い
I'm losing.
負けてる
My eyes are losing.
目が負けてる
Leave it to your seniors, leave it to your seniors.
先輩に任せる、先輩に
Senior, senior.
先輩、先輩
Put this on?
つける、これ?
This is not good at all.
なんか全然ダメだね、これ
It's not right.
あってない
strange.
おかしい
It's a travesty.
おったくりだ
This is no good.
ダメだな、これ
Let's break it.
壊そう
No, this.
ダメだ、これ
Not at all.
全然ダメ
Ayashi is cute.
あやしかわいい
My true feelings come out.
本音が出る
Is it a lighthearted music?
軽快なミュージュか
Eh, your ass is warm, isn't it?
え、ケツあったくね?
Try it, try it.
触ってみて、触ってみて
It's kind of warm.
なんかあったかいぞ
Yururi's.
ゆ るりの
It's scary.
怖いよ
toilet.
トイレ
Can it sway?
ゆれるか?
That's definitely a lie.
絶対嘘だろ
It doesn't feel too fluffy.
なんかふわってしないからな
I really felt like the Power of Terror.
めちゃくちゃパワーオブテロの気分になったな、
surely.
確かに
for a moment.
一 瞬
What are you imagining?
何想像してるの?
It's cold.
寒くて
Is it cold or do you want to use the bathroom?
寒いのか、トイレにしたいのか
It's cold, that's for sure.
寒いね、確かにね
Isn't your butt a little warm?
お尻ちょっとあったかくない?
but.
でも
Is your butt warm?
お尻はあったかい
It's warm, isn't it?
あったかいよね
It's the sunset.
夕日です
It's beautiful.
綺麗です
Hello.
こんにちは
why are you smiling?
なんであんたの笑ってるの?
They seem to get along really well.
すごい仲良さそうだね
You guys.
あんたたち
I never knew there were seniors and juniors.
まさか先輩と後輩って俺知らなかったんだけど
That's right.
そうなんですよ
actually.
実は
Actually.
実はね
Satsuki-chan is my senior.
さつきちゃんが一個の先輩なんだ
When two people like this walk around, everyone turns their heads.
こんな二人が歩いてたら、 みんな振り向いちゃうよね
no.
いや
Look, here you go.
見てごらん、ほら
見て ご ら ん、 ほ ら
It's so cute.
すごい可愛いじゃん
Look at Yuki-chan too.
ゆきちゃんも見てごらん
close.
近い
These two are beautiful.
美人だね、この二人は
Did you always play?
いつも遊んでたの?
often.
よく
Sometimes something.
たまになんか
Were you playing?
遊んでたの?
What were you playing?
何して遊んでたの?
Because I love you, let's be together.
好きだから、一緒に
Watch dramas.
ドラマ見たり
Let's eat kimchi together.
一緒にキムチ食べたり
Eating kimchi.
キ ムチ食べたり
I went to Pin On Kubu.
ピン・オン・クブ行ったり
Go to concerts.
コンサート行ったり
Do you mean live?
ライブってこと?
That's right.
そうなんだ
Well then, we're really good friends.
じゃ、ガチで仲良いね
That's amazing.
すごいね
Satsuki-chan, did you know?
さつきちゃんさ、 知ってた?
Actually, Yuki-chan, can girls go too?
実はね、 ゆきちゃんって、 女の子も行けるの?
I kind of noticed it.
ちょっと気づいてた
Did you notice?
気づいてた?
It's been revealed.
バレてるやん
It's revealed.
バレてる
I kind of noticed that.
気づいてたんだ、ちょっと
Something like this has happened since I was a student.
学生の時からやっぱりこう、 なんかあったんだ
That kind of passage.
そういう節が
It feels a little close.
ちょっと距離感が近いです
That's all.
だけです
This is some behind the scenes information, Yuki-chan,
裏情報だけど、 ゆきちゃんちょっとね、
I guess I fell in love with Satsuki-chan.
さつきちゃんのこと気に入っちゃったんだもんね
I said it though.
言っちゃったけど
Because it's cute.
可愛いから
I was worried about her because she was cute.
可愛いから気にしちゃってた
Wasn't he a senior you admired?
憧れの先輩だったんでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
How do you admire me?
どう憧れられて
happy.
嬉しい
I'm so happy to be admired by such a cute girl.
こんな可愛い子に憧れられて嬉しいよね
He really does look like a tourist guide.
ほんとになんか、 観光ガイドルみたいな顔だよね
Yuki-chan is a very cute Japanese girl.
ゆきちゃんは日本人の すごい可愛い子っていう感じ
Japanese idol.
日本人アイドル
That's what it feels like.
そんな感じだよね
But we've never seen each other's skin, right?
でもお互いさ、 肌とか見たことないでしょ?
still.
まだ
What still?
まだって何?
I had other plans besides this.
これ以外に 予定あったんですけど
There wasn't.
なかった
Are you looking forward to it?
ちょっとあんた楽しみでしょ?
I can't put out much though.
あんまりちょっと 出せないけど
It's embarrassing, but I'm looking forward to it, right?
でも恥ずかしいけど、 楽しみでしょ?
actually.
実は
fun.
楽しみ
Well, I'm the one looking forward to it the most.
まあ、俺が一番楽しみなんだけどね
actually.
実は
Well then, let's start with my senior, Satsuki-chan.
じゃあ、先に 先輩のさつきちゃんから
Yuki-chan, can I see Satsuki-chan's breasts?
ゆ きちゃん、さつきちゃんの おっぱい見れる?
Yay!
イェーイ!
Satsuki-chan, please stand up.
さつきちゃん、立ってごらん
It's so cute.
すごい可愛いね
close?
近い?
It's close.
近いね
He's quite tall.
身長結構あるもんね
How many centimeters is it?
何センチだっけ?
164cm
Yuki-chan, do you like tall women?
ゆ きちゃん、背高い女好き?
Do you like it?
好きか
I'm a little kid myself.
自分チビだもんな
Now, turn around.
じゃあ、後ろ向いてごらん
Her skin is really white.
ほんと肌真っ白だね
Don't you get sunburned?
日焼けしないの?
Sunburn.
日焼け
There are two weaker ones.
2個弱いんだよ
It's the exact opposite of me.
俺と真逆だね
Kuro-chan, come next to me.
黒ちゃん、 隣に来て
Look over here.
こっち向いてみて
Kuro-chan, look at this cute face.
黒ちゃん、 見てこの可愛い顔
Shall I take it off?
脱がしちゃおうか
Aren't your boobs big?
おっぱい大きくない?
big.
大きい
How many cups are there?
何カップある?
D?
D cup?
Dカップ?
Look straight ahead.
正面向いてごらん
I also have a D cup.
Dカップもあるんだ
That dress is so cute.
その服、すごい可愛いね
Would you like me to look at this?
こっち見てもらう?
Kuro-chan, look.
黒ちゃん、見て
Great cleaning.
すごい清掃
Yuki-chan is grinning.
ゆ きちゃん、ニヤニヤ笑ってる
It's really white.
ほんと真っ白だね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
You're looking at me like this.
こう背見られてるよ
Shall I take off my shirt for a moment?
シャツ、ちょっと脱いでみようか
That's a really cute bra.
すごい可愛いブラジャーだね
My favorite one.
お気に入りのやつ
お 気に入りのやつ
Take the ribbon.
リボン取って
This is beautiful.
これは綺麗だわ
Look at Yuki-chan?
ゆきちゃんの見てみ?
Have you seen this far?
ここまで見たことあるでしょ?
Isn't there?
ないか?
It's cute.
可愛いね
It's really white.
ほ んと真っ白だわ
Turn around.
後ろ向いて
The style is amazing.
スタイルすごいじゃん
Then look forward.
じゃあ前向いてごらん
I'll take this, but from now on.
これ取っちゃうけど、今から
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Kuro-chan, take it slowly.
黒ちゃん、ゆっくり取ってあげな
So beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗
Look, it's a nuisance.
ほら、手邪魔
It's perfectly round.
まん丸だね
The color of the chikubi is also very beautiful.
チクビの色もすごい綺麗
It looks really beautiful.
めちゃめちゃ綺麗なっぽいな
Look at Yuki-chan.
ゆきちゃん見て
Come on, show me your dick, Yuki-chan.
ほら、チクビ見せてゆきちゃん
beautiful.
綺麗
beautiful?
綺麗?
You want to lick it a little, right?
ちょっとペロペロしたいでしょ?
I want to lick it a little.
ちょっとペロペロしたいな
Are you embarrassed?
照れちゃう?
It's really beautiful.
ほ んと綺麗だわ
Are you on a diet?
ダイエットとかしてんの?
I'm a little concerned.
ちょっと気にしてる
Are you doing it?
してる?
This is armor.
これはよろいわ
So, Kuro-chan, this is it.
じゃあ黒ちゃん、これ
Pants?
パンツか
Well then, why don't you sit there for PE?
じゃあそこ体育座りしてみっかい
Take off your shoes.
靴脱いじゃって
here?
ここ?
oh yeah.
そうそう
Why don't you take off your pants yourself?
ここで自分でパンツ脱いでみ?
Did you take it off?
脱いだ?
Physical education sitting.
体育座り
Take it, Yuki-chan.
ゆ きちゃん持ってって
I'll take it.
取っちゃうよ
Smooth.
つりつる
So beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗
You want to see Yuki-chan, right?
ゆきちゃん見たいんでしょ?
Is it still bad?
まだダメなの?
Not yet.
まだダメ
Why don't you just look up at it?
それ思いっきり見上げてみ?
More and more.
もっともっと
Lean further back.
もっと後ろに寄りかがって
Butt further forward.
お尻もっと前に
It's really good.
めっちゃよい
A face with a mango taken from it.
マンゴ取られてる顔
Kuro-chan, open this.
黒ちゃん開いてみこれ
It's very pink.
めっちゃピンクだね
yes.
そう
So beautiful.
すごい綺麗
Even her shy face is cute.
恥ずかしがってる顔も可愛い
I want you to see Yuki-chan.
ゆ きちゃん見てほしい
Really beautiful.
本当に綺麗
It's so beautiful.
すごい綺麗だね
Try bringing your face closer.
も っと顔近づけてみて
Hurry up if you see it.
見たら早く
Are you excited?
テンション上がった?
I can't go on anymore.
自分ならもういけられない
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Yuki-chan is beautiful too though.
ゆきちゃんも綺麗だけどね
I saw my junior.
後輩見られちゃったね
With this hand.
こっちの手で
Why not expand it yourself?
自分で広げてみ?
Stick your butt out more.
もっとお尻前突き出して
And it's really small.
しかもすんごいちっちゃいよ
mango.
マ ンゴー
It won't fit a big penis, right?
大きいチンチャ入んないんじゃないの?
I haven't been inside yet.
まだ入ったことない
Have you never put in that much?
そんなに入れたことない?
This is erotic.
これはエロいわ
Next target.
次のターゲット
Oh, no.
え、ダメだ
Okay, Yuki-chan, stand up.
じゃあ ゆきちゃん、起立
Kuro-chan.
黒ちゃん
Let it flow to the top.
上に流してあげて
Your seniors will see you.
先輩に見られちゃうね
It's too beautiful.
綺麗すぎてる
If it were me, I wouldn't be able to do it anymore.
自分ならもうダメ
I can't get it out.
出せない
Sasuki-chan, come here.
さすきちゃん、こっちおいで
Why don't you spin around once?
一周くるっと回ってみ?
It turned around pretty quickly.
ずいぶん早く回ったね
You too will run away now.
あなたも今から逃げます
The destructive power of these two is amazing.
この二人の破壊力やばいな
You looked embarrassed.
恥ずかしがってる顔してきたね
Kuro-chan.
黒ちゃん
Let it flow?
流してみ?
Is it difficult?
難しいの?
It's been a long time since I've had snow tits.
久しぶりのゆきぱい
失敗
Failure is the best.
失敗最高だよね
Both of them are seriously stylish.
二人ともマジでスタイリーな
You look really thin.
本当に痩せてるね
You're so thin.
すごい痩せてる
Skirt is loose.
スカートゆるゆる
Well then, Kuro-chan.
じゃあ黒ちゃん
Bra or something?
ブラジャーとろっか
I want you to see my favorite senior.
大好きな先輩見てもらいなよ
I wanted to be pretty.
きれいになりたかった
I wanted to be
なりたかった
I hid it.
隠しちゃった
You're good at hiding it.
隠すのうまいね
It was perfect though.
完璧だったけど
Let me show you.
見せてごらん
There isn't.
ないじゃない
I had my hair done to the back.
髪後ろにやってた
It's so beautiful.
すごいきれいじゃん
めっちゃきれいじゃん
Which way are you facing?
どっち向いて
Show me off, senpai.
見せつけて先輩
No.
ダメ
Don't be shy.
照れるな
It's beautiful, isn't it?
きれいだよね
happy.
うれしい
I guess he's so nervous that he can't make eye contact.
緊張して目合わせられないみたいになってんじゃん
I can't let you see it, my favorite senior.
見てもらえないよ好きな先輩
It's beautiful, isn't it?
きれいだよね
I said cute.
か わいいって言った
Really embarrassed.
ガチ照れ
Well, you're definitely cute.
まあ確かにあんたかわいいわ
Sit there.
そこ座って
Boredom.
退屈割
Take off your pants.
パンツ脱いで
You're good at hiding things too.
あんたも隠し方うまいな
Did you take it off?
脱いだの?
Show me your pants.
見せてパンツ
You're wearing sexy pants.
エロいパンツ履いてんな
In the back lace.
後ろレースで
These are pants I'm proud of.
自慢のパンツだね
That skirt gets in the way.
そのスカート邪魔
Open it.
開いてごらん
You're beautiful.
あんたきれいな
Yuki-chan's Mango
ゆ き ちゃん の マ ンゴー
It's so beautiful.
すご くきれいだよ
Men are all kinds of things.
男っていろんな
More knees.
膝もっと
Look, Kuru-chan.
くるちゃんほら
I'm shy.
恥ずかしがってる
Please raise it.
上げてごらん
Stick your butt out.
お尻突き出してごらん
Kuru-chan, please open it.
く るちゃん開いてごら
yeah.
ん
Please turn to Tsuki-chan.
さ つきちゃんのほう向いてみ?
Look at Satsuki-chan.
さつきちゃん見てごらん
Come here.
こっちおいで
Do more and more.
も っともっとやって
beautiful.
きれい
It was seen.
見られちゃったね
Finally.
ついに
Deep into the hole.
穴の奥まで
You saw it all.
全部見えたよね
You can see all the way to the back.
奥まで見えるよね
It's true.
ほんとだよ
Open it yourself.
自分で開いてごらん
Look, I can see everything.
全部見えてるほら
The way you touch me is erotic.
触り方がエロいな
Satsu
さつ
Ki-chan, come with me.
き ちゃん、となりきて
Yes, both of them.
はい、2人とも
Both of them are boring.
2人とも退屈割りです
Don't line them up.
並べない
Arrange?
並べる?
Get in line early.
早く並んで
Do more.
もっとやって
Yes, please open your legs.
はい、足開いてください
More to your heart's content.
もっと思いっきり
About a while ago.
さっきぐらい
Satsuki-chan, please open up more.
さつきちゃんももっと開いて
Do it under this skirt.
このスカート下にやって
Both of you spread out as much as you can.
2人とも思いっきり広げて
Spread it as much as you can, both of you.
思いっきり広げてごらん、2人とも
I'll open this up even more.
これもっと開けるよ
Further down.
もっと下
This is a luxury.
これは贅沢だな
Both of them turned towards me.
こ っち向いて2人とも
You two are doing perverted things.
2人して変態なことしてるね
Show each other.
見せ合い
Look at each other.
お互い見てみ
Facing the front.
正面向いて
Look at each other.
お互い向き合ってごらん
Let's show each other.
見せ合いしてごらん
Erotic.
エローい
You have to show me the depths.
奥まで見せなきゃダメだよ
Really beautiful.
本当に綺麗
Because you're so shy.
すごい照れてるから
It's really beautiful.
本当に綺麗だ
Here, show me more.
ほら、もっと見せて
Please open it up more.
もっと開きなこうやって
Open your legs.
足開いて
My hands are useless.
手ダメ
Is it open?
開いてる?
Beautiful breasts too.
おっぱいも綺麗
It's embarrassing, for both of us.
恥ずかしいね、2人ともね
Well then, this time it's Satsuki-chan.
じゃあ今度は さつきちゃん
Sit down.
お座って
Yuki-chan over there.
ゆ きちゃんあっち
Well then, both of you this time.
じゃあ今度2人とも
Do one quadruple bow facing the wall.
1回壁向きに4つんばえ
yes.
そう
Butt here.
お尻こっち
Get your hands on it.
手ついて
Let's do it in front of the hair.
髪前にしよう
Both of them looked at their skirts to the fullest.
2人ともスカート思いっきら見て
Stick your butt over here.
お尻こっちに突き出して
Let me show you.
見せてごらん
what?
何?
Okay, here you go.
いいからほら
oh yeah.
そうそう
more.
もっと
Yuki-chan's feet are here.
ゆきちゃん足こっち
Both of you look at me.
2人ともこっち見て
Satsuki-chan, look here.
さつきちゃんこっち見て
Then hold it with both hands.
次に両手で持って
Butt.
お尻
Please spread it out and show it to me.
ガッて広げて見せてごらん
So show me this.
それでこっち見せて
Up to the butt hole.
お尻の穴まで
I'm getting it right.
バッチリ取ってる
No.
ダメだよ
I want to gulp.
ガクブしたいな
Next is Yuki-chan.
次にゆきちゃん
Yuki-chan more hands.
ゆきちゃんもっと手
Spread it out.
ガッて広げて
One more time.
もう一回
Both of us are doing our best.
2人とも思いっきり
This is erotic.
エロいなこれ
Okay.
いいよ
Well then, it's from my seniors.
じゃあ先輩からだな
Go be a pro.
プロちゃんとなり行って
yes.
はい
Please look at each other.
見つめ合ってください
Closer.
もっと近く
Should I be careful?
注意しよっか
Look!
見てごらん
Over here.
こっちで
You look so cute.
すごい可愛い顔してる
That's erotic.
エロいな
Erotic.
エロい
Pro-chan's?
プロちゃんの?
Satsuki's feet.
さつきちゃんの足
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Take a look here.
こっち見てみて
Yuki-chan, Chuu.
ゆきちゃん、チュー
Try it.
やってみ
noisy.
うるさい
Take your tongue out.
ベロ出してごらん
Yuki-chan, pace yourself.
ゆ きちゃん、ペースして
more.
もっと
It's Puchu.
プ チューって
Make sure to let out your tongue.
いっきりベロ出してごらん
Please lick it a lot.
いっぱい舐めてごらん
How do you feel?
どんな気持ち?
I'm really falling in love with it.
本当に好きになっちゃう
Will I really fall in love with you?
本当に好きになっちゃう?
It's very colorful.
すごい色がってる
Look, Pro-chan.
プロちゃん、ほら
Lick these breasts.
このおっぱい舐めてみ
Satsuki-chan.
さつきちゃん
Super beautiful breasts.
超きれいなおっぱい
How do you feel about your breasts?
おっぱい気持ち?
Look here.
こっち見てごらん
Yuki-chan, lick that.
ゆきちゃん、そっち舐めてみ
Breasts.
お っぱい
together.
一緒に
Lick it.
舐めてごらん
It's so hot.
めっちゃイッチ
Yuki-chan, lick me.
ゆきちゃん、舐めて
Lick my boobs.
おっぱい舐めて
Satsuki-chan, please lick it.
さつきちゃん、 舐めてごらん
hot water
ゆ
Ki-chan, please eat all of the neck and breasts.
き ちゃん、もっと地首全部 パクって食っちゃおっぱい
Lick my boobs.
おっぱい舐めて
Try putting it on your face and breasts.
顔ペタペタつけてみ、おっぱい
Show me when you get to Jiku.
地首行ったら見せて
Look, I'm standing.
立ってるから、ほら
Bing?
ビンビン?
It's bing, you see.
ビンビンだ、ほら
I became your junior.
後輩にならなっちゃったね
Jiku is doing this.
地首こんなビンビンして
I didn't want to be this cute.
こんな可愛い子にならなかった
hey.
ね
Then, put more of your butt in this direction.
そしたら、もっとお尻こっちに パーって出して
Get drunk behind?
後ろに酔っかかれる?
Kuro-chan, come here.
くろちゃん、おいで、ここ
Let's be more courageous.
もっと思い切り合えて
Yuki-chan, chew on my pussy.
ゆきちゃん、 おまんこにチューして
It's so erotic.
すごいエロい
Look at Yuki-chan's face.
ゆきちゃんの顔、ほら
Satsuki-chan, open your pussy yourself.
さつきちゃん、自分で おまんこ開いて、
Look.
ほら
Yuki-chan, reveal your tongue.
ゆきちゃん、べろ出して
Stroke all these holes.
この穴全部撫でて
Take out all the tongue and see.
べろいっぱい出して、ほら
What does it taste like?
どんな味する?
I will remain my favorite senior.
大好きな先輩のまま
delicious.
おいしい
delicious?
おいしい?
Do more.
もっとやって
Chestnut lick it.
くりぺろぺろして、くり
Look over here.
こっち見て、ほら
Just like that, see.
そうやって、ほら
It's really one piece.
めっちゃ一丁だ
Suck it, come on.
吸って、ほら
Full chest.
くりっぱい
Suck some more choo choo, here you go.
もっとチューチュー吸って、ほら
It's so erotic.
めっちゃエロいよ
Okay, now put the tongue in the hole.
じゃあ、今度は 穴の中にべろ入れて
You have to give it your all.
思いっきり出さなきゃダメだよ
Try putting it all in and use your own tongue.
全部入れてみ、自分のべろ
Satsuki-chan, do you understand?
さつきちゃん、分かる?
Does it contain tongue?
べろ入ってんのか
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Don't lick everything.
全部舐めてあげないで
Come up from below, bellon.
下から上がれて、ベロンって
Many times.
何回も
It's a great match.
めっちゃ一致だよ
Make it feel better, come on.
もっと気持ちよくして、ほら
More condensed.
もっとくりじめて
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
This is so erotic.
すごいエロい、これ
Is Mank delicious?
マンクおいしい?
One more time, here we go.
もう一回、ほら
Choo-choo, here you go.
チューチューして、ほら
Churippai, choo choo.
くりっぱい、チューチューして
beautiful?
きれい?
Will you fall in love with me?
好きになっちゃう?
You'll fall in love with it.
好 きになっちゃうね
You'll really fall in love with it.
本当に好きになっちゃうね
Shall I use the phone? Phone.
電話使おうか、電話
You're happy.
幸せだね
Licking my cute senior's pussy.
可愛い先輩のマンク舐める
I'll stay one more time.
もう一回、残っちゃうな
It's a naughty worry.
なんかエッチな心配だ
Look at my senior's naughty face.
先輩のエッチな顔見てみて
Erotic?
エロい?
Chew it.
チューしてごらん
Tateki-chan, look.
たてきちゃん、ほら
Yuki-chan, look at me.
ゆきちゃん、眺めて
More chew.
もっとチュー
Look this way, Tateki-chan.
こっち向いて、たてきちゃん
I'll cover my face.
顔かけしちゃうね
Looks like it'll be alive.
生きそうだね
Show me, let me see you live.
見せてごらん、生きてごらん
Because you're alive, Mank.
生きているから、マンク
Mank, please show me more.
マンク、もっと見せてごらん
Yuki-chan, take a look.
ゆきちゃん、見てみな
why?
なんで?
That's amazing, Yuki-chan.
すごい、ゆきちゃん
Have you gone?
行っちゃった?
Midmank, show me.
ミッドマンク、見せてごらん
Pro-chan, try shaking that way.
プロちゃん、そっち揺らえてごらん
Yuki-chan, take a look.
ゆきちゃん、見てごらん
He said he was gone.
行っちゃったって
Chew here.
ここにチューして
I'll lick your erotica.
エロを舐めてあげる
I'll lick it all.
全部舐めてあげる
midmank
ミッドマンク
I cleaned it.
を きれいにした
One more time.
もう一回
Put it up to your nose.
鼻まで入れて
Great smile.
すごい笑顔
I went there twice, Yuki-chan.
2回も行っちゃったから、ゆきちゃん
I haven't been there.
行ってない
feel ill.
気持ち悪い
It was so cute.
すごい可愛かった
Well then, it's time to take turns.
じゃあ、今度交代だよ
Look at being licked by your senior.
先輩に舐められてごらん
Please sit down.
お座ってごらん
Sasuki-chan, please come over here.
さすきちゃん、こっち行ってごらん
Become a pro.
プ ロちゃんとなり
Chew it.
チューしてごらん
Hands get in the way.
手邪魔
Pro-chan, try adding more bells.
プロちゃん、もっとベルを思いっきり入れてごらん
Erotic?
エロい?
Erotic.
エロい
Sasuki-chan and Yuki-chan should also ring the bell.
さすきちゃんが、 ゆきちゃんももっきりベルを入れてごらん
Yuki-chan needs to give out more bells, too.
ゆきちゃんももっとベルを出さなきゃダメでしょ
You're more serious, aren't you?
もっと本気でしょ
Why don't you make a lot of noise and chew?
いっぱい音立ててチューしてみ?
Try smoking it.
吸ってみよ
It's so erotic.
め っちゃエロい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
Well then, Gro-chan.
じゃあ、グロちゃん
Let's lick these breasts.
このおっぱい舐めちゃおう
Show me your pussy
おまんこ見せなが
and others.
ら
Sasuki-chan.
さ すきちゃん
Lick one breast.
片方のおっぱい舐めて
Look!
見てごらん
Look at the face of your favorite senior.
好きな先輩の顔見てごらん
Your breasts are being licked.
おっぱい舐められてるね
For such a cute child.
こんな可愛い子に
Sasuki-chan, give me more bells.
さすきちゃんもっとベルを出して
ring the bell
ベルを出
do.
して
Try smoking it nearby.
近 くに吸ってごらん
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Are you happy to be licked by such a cute girl?
こんな可愛い子に舐められて幸せなの?
I can see your pussy like this.
こんなおまんこ見えてるけど
Look towards Sasuki-chan.
さすきちゃんの方向いて
Please make more noise and let both of you suck.
もっと音立てて2人とも吸ってごらん
Breasts.
お っぱい
Look closer.
近くにしてごらん
You're standing nearby.
近くに立ってんじゃん
Did you feel it?
感じちゃった?
Don't close your legs.
足閉じちゃダメ
Sasuki-chan, come here!
さすきちゃんこっち来てごら
yeah.
ん
Hands get in the way.
手 邪魔
Try holding it close to your face.
顔に近づけてみて
You've never licked a pussy, have you?
おまんこ舐めたことないでしょ?
Not really.
ないね
Chew it.
チューしてごらん
That's erotic.
エロいね
more.
もっと
Don't let go.
離しちゃダメ
Bring out the bell.
ベルを出して
Try sucking it.
くり吸ってごらん
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Please suck louder.
もっと音立てて吸ってごらん
Look at the bell from bottom to top.
下から上までベルを出してごらん
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Please lick me more.
もっといっぱい舐めてあげて
Make more noise and lick it.
もっと音立てて舐めてごらん
Put the bell in the hole
穴にベル入れてごら
yeah.
ん
Do you know what it means to enter?
入 ってのわかる?
I understand.
わかる
Put more in.
もっと入れて
Lick it all.
全部舐めてあげて
Yuki-chan, look.
ゆきちゃんほら
Spread your pussy with your hands and do it yourself.
手でおまんこ広げて自分で
Use your hands to spread your pussy.
手使っておまんこ広げて
More the opposite.
もっと反対に
Please lick this a lot.
これいっぱい舐めてもらえ
I'm twitching.
ピクピクしてるよ
nice.
いいね
My favorite senior.
好きな先輩
Let me lick your pussy.
おまんこ舐めてもらって
I'm happy.
幸せじゃん
At the end, Krion lets out the bell all at once.
最後クリオンが一気にベルを出してごら
yeah.
ん
Was it beautifully done?
綺 麗にできた?
I licked it all.
全部舐めちゃった
Yuki-chan, look.
ゆきちゃんほら
Guess it's clear.
クリア当ててあげな
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
I'm still patient.
まだ我慢だよ
Could you please let me see where you're going?
先輩に行くとこ見てもらえない?
Are you going?
行っちゃうの?
Let's go to senior.
先輩に行こう
Spread it out a lot.
いっぱい広めて
I laughed.
笑っちゃったよ
It was easy.
楽々したね
Have her pussy spread once.
一旦まんこ広げてもらう
Let me teach you more.
もっと教え出してもらう
Look, Satsuki-chan.
見てさつきちゃんほら
copper?
どう?
Turn it over again.
もう一回ひっくりして
Satsuki-chan was so nice that I'll go again.
さつきちゃんよかったからもう一回行くとこして
You went, right?
行ったよね
Yuki-chan too.
ゆきちゃんもね
Yuki-chan here
ゆきちゃんこっち
in.
で
I go there while looking at the camera.
カ メラ見ながら行くんだよ
Look here.
こっち見てごらん
Just like that?
そのまま?
Are you heading this way?
こっち向いて行くの?
it hurts.
痛い
I'll move more.
もっと動いて行っちゃう
Yuki-chan came out though.
ゆ きちゃん出たけど
That's amazing.
すごいね
Her legs are so naughty.
すごいエッチな足出てる
Let me show you.
見せてごらん
Yuki-chan this.
ゆきちゃんこれ
That's amazing.
すごいね
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
I'm taking everything.
全部取ってる
It's soaking wet.
びしょびしょだよ
Have you been there a lot?
いっぱい行っちゃった?
Shall we go again?
もう一回行く?
Great look.
すごいほら
A lot came out.
いっぱい出た
Kuro-chan, spread it out and show me.
黒ちゃん広げて見せて
A lot came out.
いっぱい出たね
How was Yuki-chan?
ゆきちゃんどうだった?
Surprised?
びっくり?
That's amazing.
すごいね
I squirted so much.
めっちゃ潮吹いちゃったね
It was amazing.
すんげえろかったよ
Now then, to these two cute people,
じゃあ今度はさ、 このかわいい2人に、
Do you want Kuro-chan to be bullied?
黒ちゃんいじめてもらうか
I'm looking forward to it.
楽 しみだな
Come here.
こっちおいで
Well then, let's have a skirt drink, the two of us.
じゃあ2人、一回スカート飲もうか
I did that
そした
Wow, it turned out to be completely bare.
ら、 すっぽっぽになっちゃったね
Did the two of you line up once?
2人一回並ねちゃった?
It's so stylish.
すごいスタイリーだよ
Both of us.
2人とも
Kuro-chan, this is the best.
黒 ちゃん最高でしょ、これ
I got licked by two people.
2人になめられちゃった
Keep facing this way.
こっち向いたまま
Is it getting stiffer?
チクビ固くなってきた?
Then sit down below.
そしたら、下に座ってごらん
Let's get this wet, you two.
これ濡らしてごらん、2人で
Often.
しばしばしば
Kuro-chan, you got your dick licked.
黒ちゃん、チクビなめられちゃったんだね
What is this?
これなんでしょう?
quiz?
クイズ?
Quiz, what is this?
クイズ、これなんでしょう?
Which one?
どっちかいって?
Alone.
一人でね
2 people?
2人?
Both of us.
2人とも
Let's try perroning from the roots.
根元からペローンってやってみよう
mosquito.
か
Lick the tip more and more.
ど んどん先っぽになめて
Please take a look at the tip.
いっぱい先っぽ、チロチロしてごらん
Kuro-chan, do you feel good?
黒ちゃん、気持ちいい?
Keep chilling.
ずっとチロして
Yuki-chan, put it on and lick it.
ゆきちゃん、 かぶってチンチンなめちゃ
Katsuki-chan, by chance.
かつきちゃん、たまたま
Yuki-chan, suck more.
ゆきちゃん、もっといっぱい吸って
Katsuki-chan, let's have her fill her mouth as well.
かつきちゃんも、たまいっぱい口の中に入れてもらおう
Both of them are so cute.
2人とも、すごいかわいい
Chin Chin, have you gotten bigger?
チンチン、大きくなった?
Talk a lot
いっぱい喋ってごら
yeah.
ん
Even the sounds of both of them are naughty.
え っちな音だって2人とも
Chin Chin, put it all in your mouth.
チンチン、口の中にいっぱい入れて
Yuki-chan happened to be named.
ゆきちゃん、たまたまなめちゃ
amazing.
すごい
Look this way.
こっち向いて
While looking at the camera.
カメラずっと見ながら
Lick while watching.
見ながらなめる
Look this way, full.
こっち向いて、いっぱい
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Yuki-chan, please put that in your mouth.
ゆきちゃん、それ口の中に入れてもらお
cormorant.
う
Ka Tsuki-chan, doesn't it feel good?
か つきちゃん、気持ちいいでしょ?
this.
これ
Satsuki-chan is amazing.
さつきちゃん、すごい
I want you to enter all the way inside.
奥までいっぱい入ってもらお
cormorant.
う
It's already deep inside.
もう 奥まで入ってるよ
Yuki-chan, take a look.
ゆきちゃん、見てみ
Let's get Satsuki-chan's mouth.
さつきちゃんの口もらおう
amazing.
すごい
It's all the way in, right?
奥まで入ってるでしょ?
Satsuki-chan, let me lick it out.
さつきちゃん、ペロペロって出してもらおう
I lick it a lot.
それでいっぱいなめる
oh yeah
そうそう
yes.
そう
Keep facing this way.
こ っち向いたまま
Amazing, gin inch, gin inch
すごい、ギンインチン、ギンインチ
hmm.
ン
Two people, try licking the tip.
2人 先っぽペロペロしてみ
Make more noise and lick it.
もっと音立てて、ペロペロ
Sideways towards the two of them.
2人と向かって横ペロヨンペロ
While facing this way.
こっち向きながら
Face the camera.
カメラ向いて
So cute.
すごい可愛い
Always facing the camera.
ずっとカメラ向いて
Pinch the tip all the way.
先っぽいっぱいペロヨンして
too
も
Spread a lot of spit on me and lick it
っと いっぱいツバつけて、ペロヨ
Npero.
ンペ ロ
Look up.
上に向いて
Oh yeah, Satsuki-chan turned to me.
そうそうそう、さつきちゃん向いて
I was licking it at the end.
ペロってしたね、最後は
Kuru-chan, please sit down.
くるちゃん、座ってごらん
Kuru-chan, spread your legs a little.
くるちゃん、ちょっと足開いて
The two of you stay on top.
2人こっち、上のまま
Check this out, you two.
これなめてごらん、2人
Yuki-chan, please put it in your mouth first.
ゆきちゃん、先、口入れてごらん
Satsuki-chan, beside me.
さつきちゃん、横
Try throwing it sideways.
横投げてごらん
Two people sideways
2人で横ペロヨンペ
B.
ロ
Try to throw as much as you can into the area that feels good.
そ この気持ちいいところ、いっぱい投げてごらん
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Have lots of chews too.
チュウもいっぱいして
Stand up more.
もっと立てて
Kuru-chan, please stand up straight.
くるちゃん、俺、チンチン、まっすぐに立てて
Look with your hands.
手でほら
Look at the temporary part, just the two of us.
仮の部分をほら、2人で
Try throwing while chewing, you two.
チュウしながら投げてごらん、2人
While chewing with Pero.
ペロでチュウしながら
For two people.
2人で
Karen-chan and Yuki-chan.
かれんちゃんとゆきちゃん
Check it out.
チュウしてごらん
While chewing.
チュウしながら
Are you going to stand up?
立っちゃう?
Satsuki-chan, please suck it.
さつきちゃん、しゃぶってごらん
Don't you care?
気にない?
Two people, holding hands.
2人で、チンチン、手を持って
Spit on it.
ツバ垂らして
Spit on me, Chin Chin.
ツバ垂らしてごらん、チンチン
Let's have a good time together.
2人でシコシコしてごらん
By hand.
手で
Shikoshiko.
シ コシコって
Nice, Chin Chin.
いいね、チンチン
hard?
硬い?
Ching Chin.
チンチン
Well then, let's go to bed.
じゃあ、ベッドに行こうか
That's chin chin, let's stand together.
それチンチン、2人で立ててほら
Let's throw it again together.
それ2人でもう一回投げて
Yuki-chan, move your hands.
ゆきちゃん、手を動かしてごらん
Beron beron beron.
ベロンベロンベロン
It's bigger than Yuki-chan's face.
ゆきちゃんの顔より大きいよ
Satsuki-chan, hold it in your hand.
さつきちゃん、手で持って
It's really fast.
すっごいギンギンだね
Shall I put it in your pussy?
ごまんこ入れちゃうか?
I'll put it in.
入れちゃいます
I wonder if this will fit a big penis.
デッカイチンチン入るかな、これ
yes.
はい
Let me show you.
見せてごらん
Let me have some.
ちょっと持ってあげて
Try moving forward slowly.
ゆっくり前に動いてみて
Yuki-chan, please be careful with Kuru-chan.
ゆきちゃん、くるちゃんと注意してごらん
Chinchin, does it feel good?
チンチン、気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Show me your pleasant face.
気持ちいい顔見せてごらん
You look so beautiful.
すごい綺麗な顔してる
Does it feel good there?
そこ気持ちいいの?
feeling
気持
Good.
ち いい
Try moving more vigorously.
もっと激しく動いてみて
Hit it hard, chin chin.
いっぱい打ちつけて、チンチン
A very naughty waist.
すっごいエッチな腰
Look, look.
ほ ら、ほら
Look, Yuki-chan.
見て、ゆきちゃん
That's amazing.
すごいね
Kuru-chan also follows from below.
くるちゃんも下からついてごらん
My pussy is gone.
まんこいっちゃったわ
Kuru-chan, your pussy is tight, isn't it?
くるちゃん、まんこきついでしょ
Pull it out once and see.
一回抜いて、ほら
Kuru-chan, turn your head upside down.
くるちゃん、頭逆にして
Yuki-chan, sit on top of me in an M-shape.
ゆきちゃん、この上にM字乗ってね
Not Yuki-chan.
ゆきちゃんじゃない
Tataki-chan, here
たときちゃん、ここ
To.
に
Put your hands behind your back.
手、 後ろにして
You can see a lot of places inside.
入ってるところいっぱい見えるよ
Move slowly, Kuru-chan.
ゆっくり、くるちゃん、動いて
There's quite a bit in there.
そこそこ入ってるよ
Does it feel good there?
そこ気持ちいい?
Kuru-chan, please hurry up.
くるちゃん、だんだん早くしてごらん
Kuru-chan, please let me follow you more.
くるちゃん、もっとついていかせてごらん
Let's go, here.
行っちゃう、ほら
Look, when you go, go slowly and properly.
ほら、行くとき、ゆっくり行ってちゃんと
Have you gone?
行っちゃったの?
Let's go
行っちゃ
cormorant.
う
I went.
行 っちゃったんだ
Will I fit in?
入るかな?
I don't know.
わかんない
fun?
楽しみ?
It might not fit because it's big.
大きいから入んないかも
enter?
入る?
Please put it in slowly.
ゆっくり、入れてごらん
went?
行った?
Get everyone moving.
全員動かしてもらう
Yeah.
うん
Kuru-chan, move.
くるちゃん、動いて
It's all the way in.
奥まで入ってるよ
Does it feel good there?
そこ気持ちいい?
Even the two of them are cute.
2人でも可愛い
There's a lot in it.
つぼつぼ入ってるよ
Kuru-chan, please shake it more.
くるちゃん、もっと振ってごらん
Yuki-chan, you're so tight, aren't you?
ゆきちゃん、うまくきついでしょ
Yuki-chan, it's all the way inside.
ゆきちゃん、奥まで入ってるよ
Come in for a day.
一日入ってごらん
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Kuru-chan, please pull it out.
くるちゃん、抜いてごらん
Yuki-chan, I saw it earlier.
ゆきちゃん、さっき見たから
Take it with M.G.
エムジで持って
Look behind you.
手後ろについてごらん
Kuru-chan, take it slow at first.
くるちゃん、最初、ゆっくり
Slowly insert it all the way.
ゆっくり、奥まで入れる
snow
ゆき
Chan, the juice is coming out.
ちゃん、 汁出てきたよ
Kuru-chan, I'll do it faster and faster.
くるちゃん、だんだん早くしてあげる
Eat it properly.
ちゃんと味食べて
Yuki-chan, raise your butt.
ゆきちゃん、お尻を浮かして
Kuru-chan, start from the bottom quickly.
くるちゃん、下から早く
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Please add more.
もっといっぱいついてごらん
stomach
い
Please follow me.
っぱ いついてごらん
Show me the egg.
たまご、見せてごらん
The juice came out properly.
ちゃんと汁出てきたよ
Second.
2つ目
Pejam.
ペジャム
Both of them stick their butts out.
2人とも、お尻をつき出して
Stick your butt out.
お尻をつき出して
In front of the paper.
紙前にして
Kuru-chan, Satsuki-chan, let's go in.
くるちゃん、さつきちゃん、入れちゃうな
Looks super comfortable.
超気持ちよさそう
In the middle of Satsuki-chan.
さつきちゃんの真ん中
amazing.
すごい
It's small, isn't it?
狭いでしょ
Both of their butts are terrible.
お尻が、2人ともやばい
Yuki-chan,
ゆ き ちゃん、
Look over here.
こ っち向いて
Yuki-chan, does it feel good?
ゆきちゃん、気持ちいい?
It feels so good.
こういう気持ちよさそう
butt
お尻
All the holes are visible.
の 穴が全部見えてる
If you like it, it will be taken away.
気に入ってたら取られる
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Both are tough.
どっちもきついね
Yuki-chan, come this way.
ゆきちゃん、こっち向いて
This is a face that has been in use for a day.
1日入ってる顔です
Come
くる
Hey, open your legs.
ちゃん、 足開いて
Yuki-chan, sometimes I sleep completely.
ゆきちゃん、寝もたまに全部入ってるよ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
Did you go again?
また、行っちゃったの?
It's already tightened.
もう締め付けるね
It feels super good.
超気持ちいい
Satsuki-chan, turn this way.
さつきちゃん、こっち向いて
I'll put it in, dick.
入れちゃうよ、ちんちん
So cute.
可愛くて
Put it in, dick.
入れて、ちんちん
Manjul is so wet.
マンジュルで、すごいぬれぬれ
Please let Satsuki-chan's child live.
さつきちゃんの方の子、生かしてごらん
Please make me feel good.
いっぱい気持ちよくしてあげな
Are you going?
いっちゃうの?
I'm still patient.
まだ我慢だよ
Kuru-chan, can you hold back?
くるちゃん、我慢できるか?
Let me take it out once.
一回出してあげよう
stomach
い
Did you take it out?
っぱ い出した?
Follow it all the way to the bottom.
一番奥までついておく
Bring out your spirit from within.
中から精神出して
A lot came out.
いっぱい出たね
Anytime, in your penis hole.
いつでも、ちんちんの穴で
A hole.
穴が
Kuru-chan, you're not drowning yet.
くるちゃん、まだおぼれじゃないよ
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
It's still early for the break.
まだ休憩早い
You two, lick it again.
二人、もう一回なめて
Yuki-chan, talk.
ゆきちゃん、喋って
Park
パク
That's it.
って
I wish I could become an adult.
大 人になればいい
Satsuki-chan, lick me again.
さつきちゃん、もう一回なめて
Give me a lot of tongue.
ベロいっぱい出して
Close
く る
Chan, you've grown this big again.
ちゃん、 またこんなに大きくなっちゃった
Let's go to bed tonight.
今晩、ベッドに行こう
Yuki-chan, sleep.
ゆきちゃん、寝て
Put it in.
入れてほら
So slimy.
すごいヌルヌル
She wants it from Manjul.
マンジュルでもらってがってる
It's in, dick.
入っちゃったね、ちんちん
Satsuki-chan, go back to sleep.
さつきちゃん、もう一回寝て
Yuki-chan, go back to sleep.
ゆきちゃん、もう一回寝て
most
最
First time, take it slow.
初、 ゆっくりね
Mango, please make me feel good.
マンゴー、いっぱい気持ちよくしてあげな
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
This mango.
このマンゴー
It feels amazing.
すごい気持ちいい
Take it, take it a lot.
持 って、いっぱい持って
Don't come here too much.
いっぱいこっち来ないで
This guy is scary.
こいつ、怖い
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
feeling
気持ち
good.
いい
Make your face look nice.
気 持ちいい顔にしてくれ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Kuru-chan, I'm so excited.
くるちゃん、ガンガンついたわ
Kuru-chan, come on, go deeper.
くるちゃん、もっとほら、奥まで
Follow me hard.
ガンガンついて
I won't give you much.
いっぱい出してあげない
I won't let you out in the back.
ち ばん奥に出してあげない
I won't let you go deep inside.
ちばん奥に出してあげない
The two of us will go together.
2人一緒に行っちゃうよ
Yuki-chan, have you left yet?
ゆきちゃん、もう行っちゃった?
Just sleep once.
一回寝てほら
Check the sperm.
精子確認して
Did it come out?
出た?
Kuru-chan, your sperm is amazing.
くるちゃん、精子すごいね
It's the second time.
2回目だね
Do you think a lot of girls are cute?
女の子可愛いっていっぱい出るか
I feel like I can do it as many times as I want.
何回でもいけそうだね
I think I can do it many times.
何回もいけそうだね
A very naughty mango.
すごいエッチなマンゴー
Kuru-chan, can you please lick me at the end?
くるちゃん、最後舐めてもらえない?
Let's clean it up together.
2人で一緒にきれいにしてほら
Just lick it and see.
ベロベロしてほら
Yuki-chan, lick
ゆきちゃん、舐
Meme ho
めて ほ
and others.
ら
Was it clean?
き れいにできた?
How was it for both of you?
2人ともどうだった?
it was fun.
楽しかった
it was fun?
楽しかった?
They were both so cute and I was so excited.
2人とも可愛くてすごい興奮したわ
Thank you.
ありがとうね
Let's meet again soon.
また近々会おうよ
Thank you for today.
今日ありがとう
thank you very much.
ありがとうございました
bye bye.
バイバイ
バイ バイ